freehomeownerquote.com 2004-04-01

# FreeQuoteDomain.com: Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

All information that you provide is used strictly for the purpose of providing you with a quote(s). **FreeQuoteDomain.com** will never sell, give, or otherwise transfer your personal information to any person or entity other than the insurance companies, agents, and representatives selected to provide you with quotes. 

At **FreeQuoteDomain.com** , we are committed to our customers and clients. Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality service with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our customers and clients. **FreeQuoteDomain.com** guarantees that we will keep all information that you share with us strictly confidential. We will only give your information to our selected insurance companies to retain a quote. We believe that individuals have the right to be informed about the information being collected about them and about its intended use. This Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site as well as our services. 

If you choose to correspond further with us through e-mail, we may retain the content of your e-mail messages together with your e-mail address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone. This information is kept solely for the purpose of building a client history and will help us to serve you better. 

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual. 

We use Web site browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather information about our Web site users' browsing activities, in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Web site to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers. 

Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our Web site as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our Web site and evaluate our Web site's visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture your individual e-mail address or any personally identifying information about you. 

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy.
